trippy.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy

Effective Date 09/12/2011. Last Modified Date: 3/25/2019.

Trip Remix, LLC ("Trippy," "we," or "us") knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Trippy when you use the Trippy Service, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Use.

**Information We Collect**

**User-Provided Information:** You provide us information about yourself, such as your first name, last name, email, password, photo, hometown, and Facebook friend connections, if you register for a Member account with the Service, including by "following," "becoming a fan," or adding the Trippy application, etc., on a third party service such as Facebook. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service, including the names of those individuals you chat with, as well as any information in User Content you post to the Service.

**Device Identifiers:** When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store one or more "device identifiers." Device identifiers are small data files or similar data structures stored on or associated with your mobile device, which uniquely identify your mobile device and are used by Trippy to enhance your use of the Service. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by Trippy. A device identifier may convey information about how you browse the Service to us. A device identifier does not collect or share any personally identifiable information about you. A device identifier may be used in conjunction with other information in a manner that may constitute personally identifiable information. A device identifier may remain persistently on your device, to help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Service. Some features of the Service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers are impaired or disabled. Trippy may access, collect and/or store device identifiers once you enable Trippy's Services on your mobile device.

**Location Data:** When you utilize the Service by or through a mobile device, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store "location data," which may include GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device. Location data may convey information about how you browse the Service to us. Location data does not collect or share any personally identifiable information about you. Location data may be used in conjunction with other information in a manner that may constitute personally identifiable information. Some features of the Service, particularly location-based services, may not function properly if use or availability of location data is impaired or disabled.

**Facebook Connect Information:** If you sign in to the Service through Facebook Connect, you authorize Facebook to provide Trippy with basic information such as your Facebook user ID, name, email, current city, profile picture, networks, the Facebook user ID's of your friends who have also signed into the Service through Facebook Connect, and any other information you allowed to be shared with everyone (collectively the "Facebook Basic Information"). You may also give Trippy access to other information about you and your contacts from Facebook (together with the Facebook Basic Information, the "Facebook Data"). Trippy will comply with Facebook's policies regarding Facebook Data and respect your wishes regarding the same. For more information regarding Facebook's policies please refer to the Facebook Privacy Policy.

**Cookies Information:** When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Trippy help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey anonymous information about how you browse the Service to us. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

**Log File Information:** Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

**Clear Gifs Information:** When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your Trippy account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make Trippy better for our users.

**Third Party Services:** Trippy uses third party analytics services such as Google analytics and Clicky to help understand use of the Service. Third party analytics services collect the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. Third party analytics services also receive this information and their use of it is governed by their Privacy Policy. You can read the [Clicky Privacy Policy](https://clicky.com/terms/privacy).

**How We Use Your Information**

We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service.

By providing Trippy your email address, including by "following," "becoming a fan," adding the Trippy application, etc., on a third party service such as Facebook, you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. You also agree that we may send you notifications of activity on the Service to the email address you give us, in accordance with any applicable privacy settings. We may use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out or change your preferences on your account settings page. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers. You may not opt out of Service-related e-mails.

Following termination or deactivation of your Member account, Trippy may retain your profile information and User Content for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, or audit purposes. Furthermore, Trippy may retain and continue to use indefinitely all information (including User Content) contained in your communications to other Users or posted to public or semi-public areas of the Service after termination or deactivation of your Member account. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will delete all of your Facebook Data at your request.

Trippy may use certain information about you and/or your User Content internally for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing content.

Trippy reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the User Content you post on the Service. We reserve the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason, including without limitation if in our sole opinion such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Use Agreement, or to protect or defend our rights or property or those of any third party. Trippy also reserves the right to remove information upon the request of any third party.

We use cookies, clear gifs, device identifiers, location data and/or log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our Users or engineers that are associated with certain IP addresses; (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; and (h) automatically update the Trippy application on your system and related devices.

**How We Share Your Information**

**Personally Identifiable Information:** Trippy will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. Trippy may share your personally identifiable information with third parties for the purpose of providing the Service to you. If we do this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Trippy (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service, such as User Content, becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings. We may also share personal information or content with third party services, such as social networking sites, if you direct us to do so. To change your privacy settings on the Service, go to your account settings page. If you remove information that you posted to the Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Service, or if other Users have copied or saved that information.

From time to time, we may run contests, special offers, or other events or activities ("Events") on the Service together with a third party partner. If you provide information to such third parties, you give them permission to use it for the purpose of that Event and any other use that you approve. We cannot control third parties' use of your information. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, you can choose not to participate in these Events.

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Trippy will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Trippy, our Users or others.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data (including usage of Streaming services), referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Trippy services.

Trippy may allow third-party links that appear on Trippy. Trippy does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-parties without your consent. However, please note the Trippy Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, these third-parties. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such third parties for more information.

**How We Protect Your Information**

Trippy uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information and implement your privacy settings. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Trippy or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of Trippy's distributors, such as social networks and other services. Trippy is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from Trippy, at all times.

**Compromise of Personal Information**

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Trippy will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

**Your Choices About Your Information**

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Service, in which case Trippy may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by. You can review and correct the information about you that Trippy keeps on file by contacting us directly at [support@trippy.com](mailto:support@trippy.com), or use our online contact form.

**Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Trippy does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register as Members. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on Trippy. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@trippy.com](mailto:privacy@trippy.com), or use our online contact form.

**International Data Transfer**

Trippy may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. and the use and disclosure of information about you, including personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Legal bases for processing (for EEA users):**

If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws. The legal bases depend on the services of the site you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only where:

  * We need it to provide you the services, including to operate the services, provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the services;
  * It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Services and to protect our legal rights and interests;
  * You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or
  * We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place. Where we are using your information because we or a third party have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Services.

Specifically, if you decide you want to sign up for a user account on Trippy, we ask you to consent to the sharing of your personal information needed to create the account. At any time, you can request removal of your Trippy account and any posts you made on the site, as well as all related personal data. All you need to do is send an email to [privacy@trippy.com](mailto:privacy@trippy.com), or use our online contact form.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Notification Procedures**

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Service, as determined by Trippy in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on the Service to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at [privacy@trippy.com](mailto:privacy@trippy.com), or use our online contact form.

**Address:**  
Trip Remix, LLC  
735 N Milwaukee Ave #518  
Wheeling, IL 60090

**Phone:**  
312-772-5833
